{
"question": "お弁当",
"answer": "おべんとう"
},
{
"question": "晩御飯",
"answer": "ばんごはん"
},
{
"question": "昼ご飯",
"answer": "ひるごはん"
},
{
"question": "でも",
"answer": "でも"
},
{
"question": "等",
"answer": "など"
},
{
"question": "クラス",
"answer": "クラス"
},
{
"question": "プール",
"answer": "プール"
},
{
"question": "中",
"answer": "なか"
},
{
"question": "テレビ",
"answer": "テレビ"
},
{
"question": "コーヒー",
"answer": "コーヒー"
},
{
"question": "ホテル",
"answer": "ホテル"
},
{
"question": "ニュース",
"answer": "ニュース"
},
{
"question": "テーブル",
"answer": "テーブル"
},
{
"question": "カメラ",
"answer": "カメラ"
},
{
"question": "タクシー",
"answer": "タクシー"
},
{
"question": "スポーツ",
"answer": "スポーツ"
},
{
"question": "ラジオ",
"answer": "ラジオ"
},
{
"question": "ペン",
"answer": "ペン"
},
{
"question": "レストラン",
"answer": "レストラン"
},
{
"question": "テスト",
"answer": "テスト"
},
